Toni Lozano Fernández

Barcelona, Spain | aj.lozano.fernandez@gmail.com | GitHub | LinkedIn

Resume

I am a self-driven iOS Developer, life learner with professional background in electronic industry. After more than 10 years in electronic engineering, I decided to take a new path into the software industry where I discovered my passion, specially in the iOS App and game development.

I consider myself as a great team worker, decisive, objective oriented, able to face new challenges and constant learning.

Skills & Technologies

iOS development:

Swift | Xcode | Firebase | UlKit | Networking | JSON parsing | Core Data | Realm | Core Location | Auto Layout | MVC & MVVM | Cocoapods | Git | Github | Object-oriented programming | Clean code

Game development:

Unity | C# | C++ | Visual Studio | 3D | 2D | OOP | Clean code | Git | Github

Android development:

Android SDK | Java | Kotlin | Xml | MVC & MVVM | RESTful APIs | SQLite | Firebase | OOP | Git | Github

Others:

Microsoft Project | Agile methodologies | Slack | Trello | Source Tree

Experience

2016-2022 Neec Audio Barcelona Position: Hardware designer

Tasks: Responsible of hardware design oriented to Professional Audio devices whith

innovative solutions.

2014-2016 Zolertia S.L.

Position: Hardware and Firmware developer

Tasks: Responsible of all Hardware design and firmware development for products like Z1,

Re-mote, etc. Including schematics design and PCB multi-layer, component selection

and verification based on circuit simulation, prototype testing.

2008-2014 Advancare S.L.

Position: R+D Technician

Tasks: Project development in all stages of production of custom-made devices, from

planning to spec documentation, hardware design, firmware development, integration

and testing.

Academic training

2022-2022 Universitat Oberta de Catalunya

Android development course.

2018-2019 UNIR - La universidad de internet

Máster en Diseño y Desarrollo de Videojuegos.

2018-2018 Institut Obert de Catalunya

CFGS Multiplatform Application development

Software applications and data base under Java language.

2006-2008 Institut Escola del Treball

CFGS Electronic products development

Certifications & other courses

2023 iOS & Swift - The Complete iOS App Development Bootcamp

Udemy - Angela Yu

2022 Beginning C++ Programming - From Beginner to Beyond

Udemy - Dr. Frank Mitropoulos

2015 An Introduction to Interactive Programming in Python (Part 1) (Part 2)

Coursera

Two courses about interactive application development in Python.

Other

Languages English: C1

Spanish: Native Catalan: Native